NGOC GIAU LE

Date of Birth: Dec 29, 1988

Email: lenggiauit@gmail.com

Mobile: +1(437) 268-7475

Position: Net Developer

Profile Summary

I have around 10 year experience working as a senior .Net Developer in ASP.Net. MVC, API, .Net Core, Entity Framework using C# ReactJS, HTML, CSS (Bootstrap), jQuery, MSSQL, MYSQL, Web Service, IIS sites and mobile applications both iOS and Android using Flutter, Firebase.

I am able to work as a full stack developer.

My linkedin: https://www.linkedin.com/in/lenggiauit/

My GitHub: https://github.com/lenggiauit

Working Experience

Working at Titan Technology as a Senior Software Development Engineer

03/2021- Now

- Implement new features, unit test, maintain and troubleshoot issues.
- Work in production support team to support production issues.
- Analyzing and developing web API.
- Work with Agile Scrum methodologies.
- Technologies: .Net Core, .Net API ,MS SQL Server, React, Service bus, Azure services.

Worked at Aperia Vietnam as a senior .Net Developer 5/2013 – 01/2021

- Work with BA, UI/UX and Database development to develop web application, window application,
 API and parser application.
- Analyzing and developing web applications and web services.
- Implementing, unit test, maintaining and troubleshooting web applications.
- Perform a technical analysis of requirements.
- Deploy release packages to QA, UAT environments.
- Work with TFS, GIT source control, Azure.
- Support QA, UAT in troubleshooting and fix the issues with clients.
- Work with Waterfall and Agile Scrum methodologies.
- Working with Agile Scrum Projects is utilizing for tracking and managing Websites.
- Technologies: ASP.NET, Bootstrap, JQuery, MVC, .Net Core API, SQL Server, JSON, XML.

Working at Sacombank group as a .Net Developer

1/2012 — 6/2012

- Implement features for Internet banking
- Technologies: ASP.NET, Oracle, SQL Server.

Projects

Auvenir Project

03/2021 - Now

- Brief Description: This project is a big project of Deloitte Canada Client.
- Technologies: .Net Core API, SQL Server, Service bus, Azure service, React JS.

GBS CM 2019 – 2021

- **Brief Description**: This project is case management for Fiserv client. Fiserv is a provider of technology solutions to the financial world, including banks, credit unions, securities processing organizations, insurance companies, ...
- Technologies: .Net Core API, SQL Server, Web services. CI/CD automation

Vision Web system for Multi-Tenant

2016 - 2019

- Brief Description: This project is built for clients in Payment Card Industry which includes these
 functionalities: Data file processing, Merchant Boarding, Reporting modules for the clients to view
 reports of transactions, deposit, returns, retrievals/chargebacks, Risk Management module for the
 clients to detect and prevent fraudulent from their merchants, Case Management module for the
 clients to record and manage issues from their merchants, and some other efficient modules
- **Technologies**: ASP.NET, SQL Server, Parser, API, Web services ,IIS (deploy, manage sites, troubleshooting issue)

First Data Corporation and National Processing Center system

2014 - 2015

- Brief Description: These are two separate projects built for the two big clients First Data
 Corporation (FDC) and National Processing Center (NPC) to provide them with Data file processing,
 Reports, Risk Management and Case Management functionalities.
- Technologies: ASP.NET, SQL Server, Parser, API, Web services, IIS (deploy, manage sites, troubleshooting issue)

Education

• Diploma of National Institute of Information Technology

Interests

- Traveling
- Photography